Museum of the Game ®

International Arcade Museum® — Killer List of Videogames®

1. [Home](https://www.arcade-museum.com/)
2. [Legal](https://www.arcade-museum.com/legal)
3. Privacy Policy

 [](https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy)[](https://www.reddit.com/submit?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy)[](https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy)[](fb-messenger://share/?link=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy)[](whatsapp://send?text=I%20found%20this%20fun%20retro%20page%20at%20the%20Museum%20of%20the%20Game%20(KLOV):%0A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy%0A%0A)[](https://t.me/share/url?url=I%20found%20this%20fun%20retro%20page%20at%20the%20Museum%20of%20the%20Game%20(KLOV):%0A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.arcade-museum.com%2Fprivacy-policy%0A%0A)[\[email protected\]](https://www.arcade-museum.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

WebMagic Privacy Policy
-----------------------

**Updated: May 31, 2018**

_Note: Our privacy policy has been updated for the first time in several years. Effectively immediately, children under the age of 16 in Europe are not permitted to use our site (up from 14). For other regions, the minimal age had been lowered from 14 to 13. Other changes are fairly minor. We've added additional disclosure information in general -- particularly in regards to third party cookies and services, access to your own data, as well as further information on how we handle people that we believe are intentionally trying to misuse our systems. We also added emphasis to the fact that information you upload to the site for public consumption (ie: message forums or comments added to pages or videos) can not often be deleted. In such cases, we can usually assist in removing content in these posts specifically referencing your real name or contact information (except in some extremely rare cases of public warnings of alleged misdeeds by a user against other users deemed required for the protection of the community)._

**Introduction**

WebMagic, Inc. ("WebMagic") respects your private information and utilizes the following practices ("Privacy Policy") in regards to the collection and use of any information we are provided about the users of the WebMagic web sites. Please review this Privacy Policy prior to using our websites, and in particular before posting any personal information to them since our Privacy Policy may be changed periodically without notice to you. Additionally, our online Terms of Use describe the obligations and restrictions that you agree to in exchange for being allowed to use our services. They are a legally binding contract between you and us. This Privacy Policy applies to all the products, services, and websites offered by WebMagicand governs data collection and usage. Specific products, services, and websites may have additional and over-riding written policies. Additionally, content made available for licensing will be subject to our license policy. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to WebMagic include all our products, services and websites (collectively, the services). By using the WebMagic services, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

By using our services and providing personal information to WebMagic, you are agreeing to allow us to collect and utilize this information as you use our web sites, and you are agreeing to allow us to disclose that information and details of any transactions with WebMagic's offices, subsidiaries, affiliates, and payment processors. Due to the structure of the Internet, such data may pass through any country.

**Collection of your Personal Data**

In order to provide services, WebMagic may require you to provide certain information to us, and WebMagicmay collect other information automatically. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, company name, address, email, phone number, credit card information (ie: on ecommerce sites), search preferences, and preferred password. Ecommerce and message forum offerings in particular collect a variety of user data.

Some pieces of data shall be provided optionally, and some are required as a condition for registration. Required pieces of information vary depending upon the individual web site or service requested. For the few services on our network that require payment, we request credit card or other payment account information which we may maintain on our servers.

We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from our other services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by WebMagic. When you visit any of WebMagic's sites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information can include: the name and address of the page you are visiting, your IP address, browser type, browser language, access times, referring website address, and one or more cookies that uniquely identify your browser. This information is used for the operation and security of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of our web sites.

There are several ways you may obtain a copy of your own data. If this site has a message forum, you can log in, and then under 'Search' select 'Advanced Search' and search for all posts by your username. In the private messages section, there is a function at the bottom labeled 'Selected Messges'. Several options in the pick-list are for downloading your messages (in a variety of available formats). For all other personal data, if if you need further assistance, contact us directly for assistance.

**Use of your Personal Data**

WebMagic collects, stores and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and to deliver the services you have requested.

WebMagic may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

WebMagic may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from WebMagicand its affiliates.

WebMagic may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within our network, in order to determine which WebMagic services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within WebMagic to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Our Privacy Policy exists to protect all our visitors and our sites--not the rare individual with evil intent. If we, in our sole discretion, believe that any visitor(s) has or has had dishonorable intentions against us or other users on our network, we reserve the right to use any of your information in any way we see fit, in particular in ways to protect us, our other users, and society as a whole, and to inform and educate our other users. This includes any users who we suspect are spamming us or our users, data mining our sites, attempting fraud against us or our users, harassment of us or our users, or any other activity which we deem to be anti-social. In the past, we have felt the need to take this action against well less than 1/10 of 1% of our visitors. When it does happen, it usually involves a visitor trying to bring harm to message forums or other users on message forums.

**Additional Parties**

We do not share your contact information with unaffiliated third parties without your consent, except potentially in cases of limited and specific law enforcement or government request. However, you hereby grant us consent to share your information as we deem necessary for the safety of our company, sites, and other users if we believe you are using our services to attempt to defraud us or others. Historically, we have made such determinations in less than one in 10,000 users, and only shared data in a small subset of those cases.

Information you provide will be used within our company, and in cases by affiliated companies, to provide you with our services.

WebMagic may from time to time contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (such as e-mail address, name, mailing address, or phone number) is not transferred to the third party.

WebMagic may share your data with trusted partners to help perform payment processing, security services, statistical analysis, email servicing, postal mail, customer support, surveys, direct marketing, or to arrange for deliveries. Service providers will only be provided such information as is related to their roles in assisting WebMagic. Except as authorized by you, all such third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information except to provide these services to WebMagic, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information.

WebMagic's pages may include advertising operated and controlled by third parties, in particular Google and Yahoo. Their own privacy policies likely apply to this sponsored content.

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy or as you authorize, WebMagic does not disclose or release personally identifiable information to third parties; provided that, to the extent permitted by law, WebMagic may use or disclose personal information: (a) for compliance purposes, such as for customs control, security, and legal support; (b) in connection with legal requests from (i) governmental authorities or (ii) third parties pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process; (c) to perform payment or identity verifications, debt reporting or collection, or to otherwise protect the rights or property of WebMagic, its officers, employees, customers, affiliates, or end users, or (d) if we sell or otherwise transfer substantially all of our assets related to any website that we own or operate or any product or service that we offer, in which event, we will require such third party to honor our current Privacy Policy, until the third party provides you with notice of changes to the Privacy Policy and permits you to exercise any rights you may have under applicable law to limit disclosures of information about you.

Beyond the policies listed herein, WebMagic will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WebMagic or its sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WebMagic; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WebMagic, or the public.

**Web Page Links**

We do not control, nor are we responsible for, the practices employed by sites linked to or from our web sites or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. We do not endorse, approve, certify or control these sites and we do not guarantee the accuracy of the information presented on any third party site. Our Privacy Policy is not applicable to third party sites. WebMagic encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites that link to, or are linked from, WebMagic's sites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.

**Browser Cookies**

When you visit WebMagic sites, our servers may send one or more cookies - a small file that contains a string of characters - to your browser. These cookies help to uniquely identify your browser and to improve the quality of our services. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can typically only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific site or page. WebMagic uses cookies to allow you to log in and stay logged into our sites, to store user preferences, to track trends, to troubleshoot customer support issues, to provide customized content and search results, and to otherwise create and provide the highest quality of services we can. On some of our sites, they are required for even basic functioning of the site to work. Additionally, for pages that contain advertising, our advertising partners (usually Yahoo or Google) may set their own browser cookies. With the use of cookies, when you return to the same WebMagic website, the information you previously provided can often be retrieved, so you can easily use the WebMagic features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the WebMagic series or websites you visit.

**Browser Cookies - Third Party Advertising, Analytics, and Tools**

We utilize Google Adsense advertising on some of our pages. Additionally we utilize Google Analytics and Quantcast to help us understand the characteristics and demographics of people who visit our offerings. We also sometimes place 'like' or 'share' type buttons on our pages for leading social networking sites such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, or LinkedIn. These social networking leaders may or may not place cookies on your browser as a result of these buttons.  

* **Like and Share buttons** - Like or share buttons for Facebook, Instagram, Google Plus, Twitter, or Linkedin utilize functionalities provided by those respective companies. Clicking on one of these buttons will like the page content to your profile on these social media network, at least if you are logged in to those networks. These networks will then be able to attribute your visit to our pages and to your user account. Please note that as provider of these pages, we are not privy to the content of the data transmitted or used by these networks. Please contact these networks directly for their privacy policies.  

* **Google Advertising** - We may also use the Google advertising features. These features may use a third party cookie to collect information about our website traffic by tracking users across websites and across time, which generates a report for us to better understand our website users. If you do not want Google to collect and use this information you may visit the Google Ad Settings page ([https://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#!#manage-your-ads-preferences](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#!#manage-your-ads-preferences)) to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about Google ad networks and online behavioral advertising. For the Google Analytics Advertising Features, you may also opt-out of our use of Google Analytics as described above. Please remember that changing your settings with certain browsers and ad networks will not carry your privacy choices across other browsers, devices and other ad networks.  

* **Google Analytics** - We may use Google Analytics to collect information about your use of our services. This information consists of information that your web browser automatically sends to Google, such as the web address of the page that you visit and your IP address. Google may also set cookies or read preexisting cookies. This information is stored on Google's servers. Google uses this information to provide us with reports about traffic to our website and your visit to our website (such as the domain from which you access the internet, the web address of the website from which you linked to our site, the time and date of your visit to the web pages that you view and click through). We use this data to improve our website structure and content. Google may also use this data in accordance with their Privacy Policy, which can be found at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). For more detailed information on how Google uses your data through our website, please visit [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). You may opt-out of our use of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page and installing the Google Analytics browser add-on, currently made available by Google at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  

* **Quantcast** - We use Quantcast to help us understand the characteristics and demographics of the people who visit our Sites. Per Quantcast's privacy policy, Quantcast collects information about your use of our website through connecting information that your web address automatically sends, such as the web address of the page that you visit and browser time or type, with a random identifier (a cookie ID). This information is then analyzed to improve our Sites and products. Quantcast's privacy policy states that they do not link this data to your name, address, email or phone number, or otherwise attempt to discover your identity. For further information on how Quantcast works you can visit [https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/). In order to 'Opt-Out' of Quantcast go to [https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/).  

* **YouTube** - Our website uses plugins provided by the Google-operated website YouTube. The pages are operated by YouTube, LLC. A connection to YouTube servers is established when you visit one of our pages containing the YouTube plugin. The YouTube server receives information about which of our pages you have visited. YouTube will be able to directly attribute your surfing behavior to your personal profile if you are logged in to your YouTube account while visiting our pages. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account before visiting our website. Please read the YouTube privacy policy for more information about their handling of user data: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  

* **Additional Services** - We may incorporate additional third party services to our sites. If we do, their function and use is likely to be similar to the uses described by the other third party services. For example, some of our pages allow for payment via PayPal. Clicking on a payment link will take you to PayPal, and if you click to to PayPal and make a payment to us, PayPal will know you utilized our serivces, and PayPal may share basic information accompanying your payment, including your name and contact information.  

**Security of your Information**

WebMagic works to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure in multiple ways. We believe we have implemented reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, destruction or alteration of your information. Despite our best efforts though, no security measures are completely impenetrable, and we don't have as many security resources at our disposal as large media companies do.

**Age Restrictions**

WebMagic's websites and the content therein are intended for use by persons age 16 and older for visitors from Europe, and by persons age 13 and older in all other regions. WebMagicdoes not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. Anyone under the age of 16 in Europe and under the age of 13 elsewhere should not establish an account on our sites and should not provide any personal information to WebMagic. Additionally, will may provide additional restrictions for all visitors between our minimal ages and 17. Anyone under the age of 18 should not conduct any financial transaction on or through our sites, nor shall advertise for, or respond to advertising for, any financial transaction on our site, nor should provide any financial data such as credit card numbers.

**User communications**

When you send email or other communications to WebMagic, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, track pending issues, and improve our services. When you sign-up for an account, we will send you a validation email that contains a link that you will need to click on before you may use your free account. Additionally, if you join one of our message forums, you have the option (not the default) of receiving notices of updates to threads you have expressed interested, and/or notices of incoming private messages from other users. If you no longer wish to receive these forum message, turn the option off on the same settings page in which you turned it on in the first place (access via the forum user control panel or clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of any subscription email). A few of our business to business web sites (such as www.efootage.com) may send out weekly (or less frequent) emails to members that have specifically requested them. Each email has a link at the bottom you can click if you no longer wish to receive these weekly newsletters.

**Links**

WebMagic may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our offerings, customized content, and advertising.

**E-mail and Account Management**

All email sent from this system is as a result of a specific request. If you signed up on one of our sites, you will be sent a confirmation e-mail. If you do not click on the link in said email, your account will never be made active. Once made active, you may receive e-mail from us based on the preferences you selected when you signed up. To turn off any such email from one of our main sites, log in, select 'edit my account', and turn off your email settings. Additionally, any 'update' email sent out may be turned off by either the account setting page, or by clicking on the 'remove' link from the bottom of each e-mail. Lastly, by default, our message forums do not sent out email. If you have asked the system to send you email (ie: updates to threads you have posted in), and you no longer to receive such updates, you should turn them off the same way you turned them on--via account settings in the user control panel.

**Account Closures and Removal of Data**

An account closure, initiated by either you or us, may not result in the deletion of all your data. If you are utilizing one of our sites which allow users to post personal information publicly, such as in the form of a personal profile, please feel free to make specific requests regarding working to remove any such information. We will review such requests on a case-by-case basis. Please do not ask us to delete messages in bulk that you posted to public message forum threads, as it is typically not possible to remove such messages without damaging the context of the message threads in which they appear. In general, we are unable and unwilling to remove public posts on discussions forums, but are able to edit posts upon requests them to remove your name or contact information, and alter usernames if you originally chose a username that is identical to your first and last name. Personally identifiable contact information in our databases is deleted if and as required by law, however, we do not delete data for the very few users suspected of utilizing our systems to break laws or defraud others.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. Furthermore, we expect to make periodic changes to it. When we do, the only notice of said changes will occur on the policy itself. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy. WebMagic encourages you to review this policy whenever you visit our website, or at least when you intend to specifically post personal data to it.

**Privacy Policy Contacts**

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you have any concerns about our implementation of same, please feel free to contact us at:

Privacy and Data Department  
WebMagic, Inc.  
530 S. Lake Avenue, Suite 450  
Pasadena, CA 91101

An email address and phone number for communicating with us about our privacy policies may be found on this [Contact Us](http://www.webmagic.com/contact/) page.

While you may contact us regarding these policies via email, U.S. Mail, or phone, we do ask that whenever possible you contact us via email or U.S. mail, as it allows us to route your communication to the proper person without undue delay.

Please note that email may be get lost or caught up in spam protection measures. As such, if you do not receive an anticipated response to an email about this Policy, please feel free to contact us by postal mail.

**Terms of Use**

Your use of our web site or other services constitutes an acceptance of our [Privacy Policy](https://www.arcade-museum.com/privacy-policy) as well as our [Terms of Use](https://www.arcade-museum.com/terms-of-use).

Museum of the Game®
-------------------

International Arcade Museum®  
Killer List of Videogames®

### Legal

© 1995-2024 by WebMagic Ventures, LLC, The International Arcade Museum®, Museum of the Game®. All rights reserved.

Portions provided under license from the Data Refinery™.

If you wish to use material from our web sites, please take a look at our [Acceptable Use, Copyright, and Trademark Page](https://www.arcade-museum.com/acceptable-use-copyright-trademarks) . Except as described on that page, any use of the information found here may not be copied or reprinted on any medium, either physical or electronic, without the express written permission of The International Arcade Museum.
